subrass DEMO
ASS Subtitle Renderer for WebAssembly
Welcome to the subrass demo!
This showcases ASS subtitle rendering in the browser via WebAssembly.
This text is red
This text is green
This text is blue
Bold magenta text
Times New Roman 60pt
Bold text and italic text
Underlined and strikethrough text
Bottom-left aligned
Bottom-center aligned
Bottom-right aligned
Top-center aligned
Fade in over 500ms and fade out over 500ms
Complex fade with alpha control
Sliding text from left to right
Text rising from bottom to top
Gradually turning red and growing
Multi-stage color transform
3D rotated text (X:10 Y:20 Z:350)
Rotated 45 degrees clockwise
Thick border (5px)
Large shadow (5px)
No border, no shadow
Gold text with border and shadow
200% horizontal scale
200% vertical scale
Wide character spacing (20px)
Combined scaling and spacing
Text clipped to a rectangle region in the center
Inverse clip - text visible only outside center box
Blur effect (Gaussian)
Stronger blur
Maximum blur
Blur with custom sigma (5px)
This is styled as "TopComment" - appears at the top
Styled as "Credit" - italic, bottom-aligned
Small text style - great for annotations
Speaker A: Hello there!
Speaker B: Hi, how are you?
Speaker A: I'm doing great!
Multiple overrides: rotated, scaled, bold, colored
This text uses smart wrapping (q1) to avoid breaking words in awkward places
This text uses end-of-line wrapping (q2)
Line breaks only at
Modified textReset to default style
"The only way to do great work
is to love what you do."
— Steve Jobs
Thanks for watching!
Built with Rust + WebAssembly